>> 布莱恩: 当我非常，非常第一次学习 React的时候，
&gt;&gt; Brian: When I was very,
very first learning React,
其实我第一次看到 React 的时候我觉得很恶心
actually the very first time I saw React,
I thought it was gross.
我觉得很恶心，因为为什么我要把 HTML 放在我的 JavaScript里 ?
I thought it was gross because why would
I wanna put HTML inside my JavaScript?
我为什么要用这种额外的错位语言
Why would I wanna have this
extra transpiled language?
我有一堆很奇怪的感觉
There was a bunch of really weird
feelings that I got about it, and
我把所有的情绪都推倒了，这就是我的心理医生告诉我要做的。
I just pushed all the feelings down,
which was what my therapist told me to do.
不是的我开玩笑的别这样
That's not, I'm kidding, don't do that.
但我要向你解释为什么我觉得这些事都很好
But I'm going to explain to you why
I think those things are okay, but
我们要从没有转换步骤开始，没有 JSX。
we're going to start with no
transpolation step, no JSX.
没有婴儿没有包裹没有包裹
No babble, no web pack, no parcel.
什么都没有
Nothing like that.
我们将会编写原始 JavaScript React ，向您展示它是有可能的。
We're going to be writing raw JavaScript
React just to show you that it's possible.
我希望有人能这样教导我因为你会看到 JX
And I wish someone would have taught it to
me like this because you'll see that JSX
React 不做任何黑魔法
and React are not doing
any sort of black magic.
只是普通的旧 JavaScript 函数调用
It's just regular old
JavaScript function calls, and
我认为你想了解你的工具
it's my opinion that you want
to understand your tooling,
如果你不了解你的工具然后重新发送它们，对吧 ?
cuz if you don't understand your tools and
you resent them, right?
因为它们似乎增加了复杂性。
Because they just seem to add complexity.
但如果您了解这些工具所解决的问题，
But if you understand the problem
that the tools are solving,
你就会接受复杂性因为它让你易于使用，对吗 ?
then you embrace the complexity because
it gives you ease of use, right?
JX 是我的问题，我对它感到不满，因为我不理解它。
So that was kinda my problem with JSX is
I resented it cuz I didn't understand it.
希望我能教你怎么做然后你就能明白为什么
So hopefully here I can teach you what it
does and then you can understand why it
存在，因为这样写 React 真的很烦人。
exists, because it's really
annoying to write React like this.
但你可以
But you can.
好吧我要你做什么我要去我的桌面
Okay, so what I want you to do,
I'm just gonna go to my desktop,
我要去做个目录
and I'm gonna make a directory.
其实就是这样说，我就说，
Actually, even just do it this way,
I'll just say,
新文件夹就会被称为 " 我的项目" 。
New folder right there, and this is
going to be called the adopt me project.
请选择其他名称。
Choose a different name.
那我就把那个删了
Well, I'm just gonna delete that one then.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，搬去 " 废纸篓"
&gt;&gt; Brian: All right, move to Trash.
好吧好吧
All right.
这一款将被称为收养
This one is going to be called adopt-me,
这才是我们今天要做的
cuz that's going to be
what we're building today.
宠物收养应用程序。
A pet adoption application.
好了我要用 Visual Studio 代码打开它
Okay, and then I'm going to open
this with Visual Studio Code.
>> 布莱恩: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: All right.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，所以现在我在这个文件夹里没有任何东西。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so now I'm inside of
this adopt-me folder with nothing in it.
我要在这里创造一个新目录
I'm gonna create a new
directory inside of here.
因此， SRC 是我刚刚创建的目录的名称。
So it's gonna be, SRC is the name of
the directory that I just created.
你没有理由这样做一个 React 项目。
There's no reason you have to
structure a React project this way.
这只是我习惯写代码的一种方式。
This is just a way that I'm
habituated to writing code.
好吧在这里我要创建一个新的文件
So okay, inside of here I'm
gonna create a new file, and
它会被称为 index.html
it's gonna be called index.html.
> > 布莱恩: 现在我要给你看的第一个窍门
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now the first trick
here that I'm gonna show you
" Visual Studio Code " 是一个叫艾美特的小东西
with Visual Studio Code is
a little thing called Emmet.
所以如果我把 html : 5，你可以看到我有这个自动完成的自动完成，
So if I put html:5, and you can see that I
have this auto completion coming out, and
如果我点击 Tab 键，它就会自动完成，就像 HTML 文件的支架一样。
if I hit Tab, it's going to autocomplete
out to like a scaffold of the HTML file.
因为我记不起需要进入 HTML 文件的所有东西，对吗 ?
Because I can't remember everything that
needs to go into an HTML file, right?
我每次都要把它给谷歌
I literally have to Google this
every single time that I do it,
所以才这么做
so that's what that does.
我会在继续使用 Emmet 的同时，我也会把它叫做 " Emet " 。
And I'll be using Emmet a little bit more
as we go on, and I'll call it out so
您可以看到它，但是您可以看到整个备忘单 @emmet.io。
you can see it, but you can see that
the entire cheat sheet @emmet.io.
你可以把 Emmet 放到Sub石灰里
It's not something that VS code invented,
so you can put Emmet into Sublime and
JetBrains 之类的东西，但它是内置在球棒上的。
JetBrains and stuff like that,
but it is built-in off the bat.
好的我会的这就叫 ADOPTme 了
Okay, and I'm gonna,
this is gonna be called ADOPTme, so
这就是我要称呼的名字
that's what I'm gonna call the title.
> > 布莱恩: 好的，在身体里，我要放几个标签。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, so here inside the body,
I'm gonna put a couple of tags.
第一个是我要放一个叫 root的人
The first one is I'm gonna
put one called root.
所以你可以给我写根的 css 选择器
So you can there I just wrote
the css selector for root,
我想当个迪夫对吧
which I wanted to be a div, right?
所以我做了 #root，然后我点击 Tab 键，然后它就能完成到一个区。
So I do #root, and then I hit Tab, and
it's gonna complete that out to a div.
现在你知道 Emmet 更复杂了
Now just so you know Emmet is
way more complicated that,
你可以和艾美特一起做疯狂的事
you can do crazy stuff with Emmet.
我就像偷懒的缩写大部分都是这样
I just use like the lazy abbreviations,
that's mostly it.
好的，所以我把 div 作为一个路线的概念，我不会把它放进去。
Okay, so I have div as an idea of route,
I'm gonna put not rendered inside of that.
我这样做的原因是，如果我看到没有呈现，我知道 React
Reason why I do that is because if I
see not rendered I know that the React
应用程序未启动。
application didn't start.
但如果它启动了，它就会取代这个区的所有东西。
But if it did start, then it's going to
replace everything inside of this div.
>> 布莱恩: 好的，在这个下面我要放两个脚本标签
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, underneath this,
I'm gonna put two script tags, so
我要把 script:src ，就这样
I'm gonna put script:src, like that.
>> Brian: 它自动完成到脚本标记。
&gt;&gt; Brian: It autocomplete
out to a script tag.
我们会把两个 URL 放在这里
And we're gonna put two URLs here.
其中一个将是 https://unpkg.com。
So one of them is gonna
be https://unpkg.com.
>> Brian: 这是 NPM 软件包的 CDN ，这只是一种时髦的说法
&gt;&gt; Brian: This is a CDN for NPM packages,
which is just a fancy way of saying
有一堆我会解包的 JavaScript 文件
that there's a bunch of JavaScript
files that I'll unpackage and
它会把这些从 mpm 的注册中拉出来
it'll pull these off of the mpm registry.
所以我要从登记册上撤下雷法
So I'm gonna pull off of the registry,
React, and
我要去找个特定版本的
I'm gonna grab a specific version,
so 16.8.4,
我认为 6 是这个拍摄的最新版本。
I think 6 is the latest version
as of the filming of this.
但我们要坚持 4 号因为我所有的笔记都在用 4
But we're gonna stick with 4 because
all my notes are using 4, so
我们还是继续吧
let's just stick with that.
>> Brian: 好的， React to
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, and React to
16.8.4/umd/reet.development.js.
16.8.4/umd/react.development.js.
> > 布莱恩: 那么这事要做的，就是去 CDN，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So what this is gonna do,
this is gonna go out to the CDN,
请抓取该文件，该文件是已编译的 React 文件，并且
grab this file which is
a compiled React file, and
它会将此作为顶级 React 变量装入，因此您可以使用 React。
it's going to load this as a top level
React variable, so you can use React.
好吧我们需要另外一个
Okay, we're gonna need
another one of this.
所以我要复制这件然后再把它贴在下面
So I'm going to copy this and
paste it underneath it again, and
那我要换两件事情
then I need to change two things.
其中一个是在提出这种反应的时候
One of them here the React
when put this react-dom,
比如， >> 布莱恩: 然后我也在上面写着
like that,
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then I'm also where it says
再反反派我要把它的反应做个反应
react.development.js, I'm gonna put
react-dom.development.js, right?
所以我在两个地方改变了这个
So I changed this in two places.
> > 布莱恩: 好吗 ? 而且
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay?
And
这将会加载一个第二个图书馆，
this is going to load a second library,
which is going to be the react-dom
库，它允许您呈现浏览器并对其作出反应。
library, which allows you to render and
react to the browser.
为什么有两个包裹呢 ?
Now why is there two packages?
看起来有点困惑对吧
That seems a little confusing, right?
你们中的一些人可能熟悉名为 " React Native" 的项目。
Well, some of you may be familiar
with the project called React Native.
因此， React Native and ReactDOM 都共享 React 软件包。
So React Native and
ReactDOM both share the React package.
这一反应就像
This React is just like,
它是一个非常小的 2 千字节的包装，说明如何与 React 交互。
it's a very small 2 kilobyte package
of how to interact with React.
所以它有你要调用的所有顶级方法
So it has all of the top level
methods that you're going to call, and
那么 ReactDOM 实际上是把所有东西都从 React 中取出来的
then ReactDOM is actually the large one
that takes all that stuff out of the React
打包并将其呈现给浏览器。
package and renders it to the browser.
根据同一令牌，您将装入 React ，并且
By the same token you would load React,
and
然后， React Native 会将其装入到 Android 或 iOS 应用程序中。
then React Native would actually load
it into your Android or iOS app.
有道理吗
Does it make sense?
好的。
Okay.
这就是为什么那里有两种不同的包装。
So that's why there's two
different packages there.
> > 布莱恩: 在我们要放置第三个脚本标签的下面，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Underneath that we're
gonna put a third script tag, and
我们会做你不该做的事
we're gonna do what you should never do,
我们要用 HTML 直接写 JavaScript
which is we're going to write
JavaScript directly in our HTML.
我告诉你怎么做是因为我想告诉你
Now the reason why I showed you how to do
this is because I wanted to show you that
这可能是超光秃秃的对吧
this can be super bare-bones, right?
我们会把它修好但现在我只想让你写这个
We're gonna fix this in a little bit but
for now I just want you to write this,
你的密码就会在这里
your code is going to go here.
>> Brian: 现在。
&gt;&gt; Brian: For now.
好了别这样了
Oops, stop that.
>> 布莱恩: 现在我做了这个，保存这个文件，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now that I've done this,
save this file, right?
> > 布莱恩: 我想让你去你最喜欢的浏览器
&gt;&gt; Brian: And I want you to go
over to your favorite browser,
我碰巧是火狐
mine happens to be Firefox.
我要在这里说 " 文件 > 打开 > 打开文件，就在那儿。
And I'm gonna go here and
say File &gt; Open &gt; Open File, right there.
>> Brian: 让我们在此处的新目录中看到此内容。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Let's see this
in a new directory here.
文件 > 打开文件，以及
File &gt; Open File, and
然后我就会浏览到我的桌面上的目录
then I'm gonna navigate to my
directory which is on my desktop.
我要找到 ADOPTme ， source和 index.html。
I'm going to find ADOPTme,
source, and index.html.
我在我的浏览器中打开了这个
And I opened this in my browser.
> > 布莱恩: 你应该看到一些没有呈现的东西，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: And you should see something
that says not rendered, right?
因为我们还没做任何事
Because we haven't actually
done anything yet.
我们刚装了图书馆
We've just loaded the libraries.
> > 布莱恩: 但是我要在这里打开我的控制台。
&gt;&gt; Brian: But
I'm gonna open my console here.
这有点大
This a bit bigger.
你不用这么做我只是在给你看
You don't have to do this,
I'm just showing you.
如果我在控制台里呆着我说 " 雷法"
If I go in here in my console,
and I say React,
因为我们装了这个，对吧 ?
now this is defined because
we loaded that, right?
使用其中一个脚本标记。
With one of the script tags.
和 ReactDOM一样
Same thing here with ReactDOM,
也因为我们把它从 CDN 中装入了
also defined because we
loaded this off of the CDN.
让人感觉所有这些都是垂直的，很酷。
Makes sense of how all that's
is plumbed together, cool.
>> 布莱恩: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: All right.
我接下来要你做的就是去拿 CSS
The next thing I want you to do
is we're gonna go grab the CSS.
这绝对不是 CSS 的问题，所以我们给所有 CSS 预先写了
This is definitely not a course about CSS,
so we prewrote all the CSS for
你这样你就不用写了
you, so that you don't have to write.
所以如果你遵循我们的约定和命名模式
So if you just follow our conventions and
naming patterns,
你会免费得到所有造型的
you're gonna get all the styling for free.
我不想让你们看这个 CSS 或者
And I'm not telling any of
you to look at the CSS or
应该是你写 CSS的方法
think it's the way that
you should write CSS.
CSS没有任何评论。
There's no commentary
intended from the CSS.
所以如果你进了课你就会看到
So if you go here into the class notes,
you're gonna see here
大约三分之一的时间，您需要抓取 CSS 文件。
about a third of the way down,
you'll need to grab the CSS file.
我们写了这样你就不用在这里下载了
We wrote it so
you don't have to download it here.
事实上坦纳写的很感谢你坦纳
And actually, Tanner wrote it so
thank you, Tanner.
因此，如果您在此处单击 " 下载 " ，那么它应将您转至该文件，
So if you click Download it here,
it should take you to this file,
你可以看到它在 GitHub上
you can see here it's
actually on the GitHub.
> > 布莱恩: 我要点击命令 A，选择所有内容，并将其复制。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And I'm just gonna hit command
A, select everything, and copy it.
然后我要回到我的项目上
And then I'm going to go back
over to my project here,
在源目录中创建新文件，
create a new file in the source directory,
叫 style.css ，并将所有业务粘贴到该文件中。
called style.css, and
paste all that business in there.
省省吧
And Save it.
好了我要把它放在头标签里
Okay, here inside of the head
tag I'm gonna put link,
我要把这一切都结束了我要把它放在一起
which is going to complete out to this,
and I'm gonna put /style.css
> > Brian: Cool.
&gt;&gt; Brian: Cool.
所以现在我们应该可以回到我们的 ADOPTme
So now, we should be able
to go back to our ADOPTme,
刷新页面现在它看起来好多了
refresh the page, and
now it looks a lot nicer.
背景中只有很少的鸡和甲壳虫，这很令人愉快。
It's got little chickens and beetles
in the background, it's very pleasant.